A Guide to the Papers of the Proctor of the University of Virginia, (Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough), 1817-1828
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Tho[ma]s May to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1825 August 26, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 5:532)
- Thomas Jefferson to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough re: importing building materials [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-2229] 1825 August 30, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 5:533)
- Bernard Peyton to [Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough] 1825 September 3, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 5:534)
- W[illiam] J. Coffee to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1825 September 4, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 5:535)
- Coleman Sellers and Joseph Saxton to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough re: clock and bell 1825 September 4, ALS, 2 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 5:536)
- Jonathan Thompson to Thomas Jefferson; endorsed. [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-2233] 1825 September 9, ALS, 2 p. with docket (Box-folder 5:537)
- Thomas Jefferson to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-2235] 1825 September 13, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 5:538)
- Account of University with Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough, 1825 January 1 - 1825 September 14 1825 September 15, AD, 5 p. with docket (Box-folder 5:539)
- Matthias E. Sawyer to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1825 September 16, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 5:540)
- Daniel Chandler to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1825 September 17, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 5:541)
- Tho[mas] Brockenbrough to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1825 September 19, ALS, 2 p. with docket (Box-folder 5:542)
- Copy of reminiscences of Jefferson re: riots [1825 September 19], TLS. 4:00 PM. (Box-folder 5:543)
- Thomas Jefferson to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough, with statements of library funds and debts of general fund [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-2237] 1825 September 20, ALS, 2 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 5:544)
- H[enry]; A[lexander]; S[cammell] Dearborn to Thomas Jefferson; endorsed by Thomas Jefferson [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-2239] 1825 September 22, ALS, 3 p. with docket (Box-folder 5:545)
- Balance sheet of the University as of 1825 September 30, signed by Martin Dawson 1825 September 30, ADS. 2 p. with docket (Box-folder 5:546)
- General statement of the fund of the University of Virginia and the application of it 1825 September 30, AD, 2 p. with docket (Box-folder 5:547)
- Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 's copy of Thomas Jefferson's queries on the state of University funds; endorsed by Thomas Jefferson 1825 September, AD, 2 p. with docket (Box-folder 5:548)
- Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough to Thomas Jefferson; with ALS, W[illiam] J. Coffee to [Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough] on verso [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-2440] 1825 October 1, ALS, 2 p. with docket (Box-folder 5:549)
- Thomas Jefferson to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-2241] 1825 October 1, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 5:550)
- Jonathan Thompson to Thomas Jefferson [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-2242] 1825 October 3, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 5:551)
- Thomas Jefferson: Resolutions of Board of Visitors; endorsed by Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-2245] 1825 October 7, ADS. 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 5:552)
- Bernard Peyton to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1825 October 8, ALS, 2 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 5:553)
- Thomas Jefferson to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-2246] 1825 October 9, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 5:554)
- Thomas Jefferson to the Board of Visitors [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-2248] 1825 October 12, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 5:555)
- Bond to U.S. signed by Thomas Jefferson, John H[artwell] Cocke, James Madison, Chapman Johnson, James Breckenridge, George Loyall, and Joseph C[arrington] Cabell [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-2249] 1825 October 12, DS. 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 5:556)
- Joseph L. Coltman to [Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough] 1825 October 13, ALS, 2 p. with docket (Box-folder 5:557)
- John H[artwell] Cocke to [Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough] 1825 October 14, ALS, 2 p. with docket (Box-folder 5:558)
- C. E. Haynes to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1825 October 14, ALS, 2 p. with docket (Box-folder 5:559)
- Bernard Peyton to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1825 October 17, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 5:560)
- Bernard Peyton to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1825 October 19, ALS, 2 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 5:561)
- H[enry]; A[lexander]; S[cammell] Dearborn to Thomas Jefferson; endorsed by Thomas Jefferson. 2 enclosures: bill from Henry Hovey & Co.; Franklin Insurance Co. [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-2253] 1825 October 21, ALS, 4 p. with docket (Box-folder 5:562)
- Thomas Jefferson to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-2252] 1825 October 21, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 5:563)
- G[eorge] Tucker to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1825 October 24, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 5:564)
- B[ernard] Peyton to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough, with diagram of column bases 1825 October 26, ALS, 2 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 5:565)
- G[eorge] Tucker to [Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough] 1825 November 1, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 5:566)
- Martin Dawson to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1825 November 9, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 5:567)
- [William Dandridge] to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1825 November 10, AL. 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 5:568)
- G[eorge] Tucker to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1825 November 10, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 5:569)
- Thomas Jefferson to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-2258] 1825 November 12, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 5:570)
- B[ernard] Peyton to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1825 November 12, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 5:571)
- Thomas Jefferson to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough; originally enclosed letter from H. A. S. Dearborn [1825 October 21] [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-2260] 1825 November 15, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 5:572)
- Jonathan Thompson to Thomas Jefferson; endorsed by Thomas Jefferson. Attached to 1825 November 12, W. Dandridge to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-2261] 1825 November 17, ALS, 2 p. with docket (Box-folder 5:573)
- F[rancis]; W[alker] Gilmer to [Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough] 1825 December 1, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 5:574)
- Reynolds Chapman to [Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough] 1825 December 5, ALS, 2 p. with docket (Box-folder 5:575)
- John Van Lew & Co. to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough, with ALS Tho[mas] Brockenbrough to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1825 December 5, ALS, 3 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 5:576)
- Tho[ma]s May to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1825 December 12, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 5:577)
- Thomas Jefferson to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough, includes proposal to establish a post office at the University [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-2266] 1825 December 13, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 5:578)
- G[eorge] Tucker to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1825 December 18, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 5:579)
- Chiles Terrell to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1825 December 20, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 5:580)
- Rob[ert] Johnston & Son to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1825 December 26, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 5:581)
- Thomas Jefferson to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-2268] 1825 December 27, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 5:582)
- Deed of land sold by Daniel F. and Mary A.F. Piper to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough for the University; copied by Thomas Jefferson [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-2270] 1825, AD, 3:00 PM. (Box-folder 5:583)
- Estimate of the expenses of the University for one year by Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1825, ADS. 2 p. with docket (Box-folder 5:584)
- Library fees, signed by John V. Kean 1825, ADS. 2 p. with docket (Box-folder 5:585)
- Library fines 1825, AD, 2 p. with docket (Box-folder 5:586)
- Miscellaneous receipts 1825, ANS. 88 items. (Box-folder 5:587)
- J[ohn] M. Perry to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1825, ALS, 1 p. with address (Box-folder 5:588)
- Thomas Jefferson's statement of cash advanced to professors of the University [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-2271] 1825, AD, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 5:589)
- Workman's papers - venetian blinds 1825, AD, 3 items. (Box-folder 5:590)
- Thomas Jefferson to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough re: bells [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-2273] 1826 January 3, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 6:591)
- Camak & Ragland to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1826 January 23, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 6:592)
- B[ernard] Peyton to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough, receipts on verso 1826 February 2, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 6:593)
- J[ohn]; P[atton] Emmet to [Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough] re: faculty resolutions 1826 February 5, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 6:594)
- Will[iam] Bolling to [Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough] 1826 February 9, ALS, 2 p. with docket (Box-folder 6:595)
- John P[atton] Emmet to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1826 February 14, ALS, 1 p. with address (Box-folder 6:596)
- Tho[ma]s May to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1826 February 21, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 6:597)
- Philip. Sturtevant to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1826 February 26, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 6:598)
- John Van Lew & Co. to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1826 March 2, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 6:599)
- Bernard Peyton to [Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough] 1826 March 10, ALS, 2 p. with docket (Box-folder 6:600)
- Rob[er]t Johnston & Son to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1826 March 14, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 6:601)
- D. W. & C. Warwick to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1826 March 16, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 6:602)
- Bernard Peyton to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1826 March 24, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 6:603)
- P. Minor to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1826 March 30, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 6:604)
- University financial statement [by Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough ] [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-2305] 1826 March 31, AD, 4 p. with docket (Box-folder 6:605)
- Bernard Peyton to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1826 April 3, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 6:606)
- Bernard Peyton to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1826 April 8, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 6:607)
- C[harles] Bonnycastle to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1826 April 10, ALS, 2 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 6:608)
- J[ohn]; P[atton] Emmet to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough [1826] April 12, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 6:609)
- John P[atton] Emmet to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough re: faculty resolutions 1826 April 16, ALS, 1 p. with address (Box-folder 6:610)
- Bernard Peyton to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1826 April 19, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 6:611)
- Ch[arles] Carey to Robley Dunglison 1826 April 28, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 6:612)
- B[ernard] Peyton to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1826 April 22, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 6:613)
- Bernard Peyton to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1826 April 29, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 6:614)
- John P[atton] Emmet to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1826 May 2, ALS, 1 p. with address (Box-folder 6:615)
- Thomas Jefferson to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-2316] 1826 May 2, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 6:616)
- Thomas Jefferson to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-2317] 1826 May 5, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 6:617)
- John Brockenbrough to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1826 May 9, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 6:618)
- John P[atton] Emmet to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1826 May 11, ALS, 1 p. with address (Box-folder 6:619)
- John P[atton] Emmet to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1826 May 12, ALS, 1 p. with address (Box-folder 6:620)
- B[ernard] Peyton to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1826 May 15, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 6:621)
- J[ohn]; P[atton] Emmet to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1826 May 16, ALS, 1 p. with address (Box-folder 6:622)
- John Van Lew & Co. to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1826 May 19, ALS, 3 p. with docket (Box-folder 6:623)
- P. Minor to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1826 May 20, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 6:624)
- B[ernard] Peyton to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1826 May 24, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 6:625)
- Bernard Peyton to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1826 May 27, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 6:626)
- John Van Lew & Co. to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough, with bill 1826 May 29, ALS, 2 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 6:627)
- Bernard Peyton to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1826 May 29, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 6:628)
- Thomas Jefferson: Instructions to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough, includes sketch of typanum of portico of Rotunda; endorsed by Thomas Jefferson [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-2324] [1826 May], AD, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 6:629)
- John Patterson to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1826 June 1, ALS, 2 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 6:630)
- Bernard Peyton to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1826 June 3, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 6:631)
- Edw[ard] Lowber to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1826 June 9, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 6:632)
- B[ernard] Peyton to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1826 June 10, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 6:633)
- Daniel Warwick to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1826 June 12, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 6:634)
- A. H. Brooks to [Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough] 1826 June 13, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 6:635)
- Bernard Peyton to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1826 June 14, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 6:636)
- A. H. Brooks to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1826 June 19, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 6:637)
- V[alentine] W. Southall to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1826 June 19, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 6:638)
- H[enry]; A[lexander]; S[cammell] Dearborn to Thomas Jefferson [original in Jefferson Papers] 1826 June 21, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 6:639)
- Thomas Jefferson to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough re: Rotunda clock. File draft, endorsed by T.J. [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-2327 item 2 of 2] 1826 June 22, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 6:640)
- Thomas Jefferson to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough; same as preceding item [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-2327 item 2 of 2] 1826 June 22, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 6:641)
- B[ernard] Peyton to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1826 June 24, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 6:642)
- Bernard Peyton to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough, receipt on verso 1826 June 27, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 6:643)
- Bernard Peyton to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1826 July 12, ALS, 1 p. with address (Box-folder 6:644)
- P[hilip] Sturtevant to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1826 July 13, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 6:645)
- John H[artwell] Cocke to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1826 July 17, ALS, 2 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 6:646)
- H[enry]; A[lexander]; S[cammell] Dearborn to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1826 July 17, ALS, 2 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 6:647)
- W[illia]m H. Richardson to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1826 July 28, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 6:648)
- Joseph Antrim's proposals for plastering 1826 August 7, ADS. 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 6:649)
- Joseph Coolidge, Jr. to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough, with attached 1826 September 22 receipt signed Joseph Coolidge 1826 August 7, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 6:650)
- Joseph Coolidge, Jr. to Alexander Garrett 1826 August 7, ALS, 2 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 6:651)
- John P[atton] Emmet to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1826 August 11, ALS, 1 p. with address (Box-folder 6:652)
- Bernard Peyton to [Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough] 1826 August 23, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 6:653)
- Joseph Coolidge, Jr. to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough re: ventilation of clock room 1826 August 25, ALS, 3 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 6:654)
- Robley Dunglison to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1826 September 8, ALS, 2 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 6:655)
- Tho[ma]s May to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1826 September 11, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 6:656)
- John P[atton] Emmet to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1826 September 20, ALS, 1 p. with address (Box-folder 6:657)
- H[enry]; A[lexander]; S[cammell] Dearborn to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1826 September 26, ALS frag. 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 6:658)
- John H[artwell] Cocke to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1826 September 27, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 6:659)
- Memorandum of glass ordered from Boston for Rotunda and [Anatomical] Hall 1826 September 28, AD, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 6:660)
- Tho[ma]s May to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1826 September 30, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 6:661)
- Joseph Coolidge, Jr. to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1826 October 3, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 6:662)
- W[illiam] Dandridge to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1826 October 7, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 6:663)
- John P[atton] Emmet to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1826 October 17, ALS, 1 p. with address (Box-folder 6:664)
- Tho[ma]s May to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough, with bill 1826 October 17, ALS, 2 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 6:665)
- C. & A. Warwick to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough, receipt on verso 1826 October 18, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 6:666)
- Reynolds Chapman to [Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough], with forwarding note, 1826 October 28, from Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough to W. L. Vowles, 1 p. with addr 1826 October 19, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 6:667)
- T[homas] H. Key to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough - money draft for Mr. Wheat 1826 October 19, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 6:668)
- Coleman Sellers to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1826 October 20, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 6:669)
- Coleman Sellers to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1826 October 23, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 6:670)
- John P[atton] Emmet to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1826 October 27, ALS, 1 p. with address (Box-folder 6:671)
- Dan[ie]l Warwick to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough, with bill 1826 October 28, ALS, 2 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 6:672)
- C. & A. Warwick to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough, receipt on verso 1826 October 31, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 6:673)
- C[harles] Bonnycastle to [Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough] 1826 November 2, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 6:674)
- W. Clarke to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough, with draft reply by Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1826 November 3, ALS, 2 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 6:675)
- Philip. Sturtevant to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1826 November 5, ALS, 2 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 6:676)
- Tho[ma]s May to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1826 November 6, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 6:677)
- G[eorge] Tucker to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough, receipt on verso 1826 November 6, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 6:678)
- John P[atton] Emmet to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough - faculty resolution 1826 November 10, ALS, 1 p. with address (Box-folder 6:679)
- John Van Lew & Co. to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1826 November 19, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 6:680)
- John P[atton] Emmet to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1826 November 21, ALS, 1 p. with address (Box-folder 6:681)
- Board of Visitors to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough - resolutions 1826 November 27, ADS. 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 6:682)
- G[eorge] Tucker to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1826 November 30, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 6:683)
- John P[atton] Emmet to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1826 November, ALS, 1 p. with address (Box-folder 6:684)
- Tho[mas] Brockenbrough to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1826 December 2, ALS, 2 p. with docket (Box-folder 6:685)
- John Tayloe Lomax to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough - money draft for Charles Tayloe 1826 December 5, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 6:686)
- Tho[ma]s May to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1826 December 7, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 6:687)
- Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough to the Rector and Visitors - "A statement of the debts and resources of the University on the 1st of October 1826" 1826 December 11, ADS. 4 p. with address (Box-folder 6:688)
- Library fines 1826 December 12, AD, 3 p. with docket (Box-folder 6:689)
- C. Tyler's directions for hanging bell 1826 December 16, ADS. 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 6:690)
- Bernard Peyton to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1826 December 20, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 6:691)
- Th[omas] W. Maury to John Tayloe Lomax, with forwarding note, 1826 December 21, from John Tayloe Lomax to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough, 1 p 1826 December 21, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 6:692)
- Martin Hart to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1826 December 29, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 6:693)
- John P[atton] Emmet to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1826 Sunday 9th, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 6:694)
- Miscellaneous receipts 1826, ANS. 65 items. (Box-folder 6:695)
- Subscriptions for a minister at the University 1826, AD, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:696)
- Joseph Coolidge, Jr. to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1827 January 11, ALS, 2 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 7:697)
- C[harles] B. Lomax to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough, with addendum, 1827 January 27, signed John Tayloe Lomax, 1 p 1827 January 13, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 7:698)
- Robley Dunglison to J. Dobson 1827 January 20, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 7:699)
- James Madison to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough [original in Madison Papers] 1827 January 23, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:700)
- Philip. Lightfoot to [Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough] 1827 January 29, ALS, 2 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:701)
- Tho[ma]s C. Jenkins to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1827 January 31, ALS, 2 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:702)
- C[hapman] Johnson and Joseph C[arrington] Cabell to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1827 February 7, ALS, 3 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 7:703)
- James Madison to [Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough] 1827 February 12, ALS (copy). 1:00 PM. (Box-folder 7:704)
- W[illia]m Wertenbaker to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough re: faculty resolution 1827 February 21, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 7:705)
- [Judge] John Coalter to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1827 February, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 7:706)
- Joseph Coolidge, Jr. to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough re: clock 1827 March 8, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:707)
- P. Haxall to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1827 March 12, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 7:708)
- J.S.M. [John S. May] to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1827 March 18, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 7:709)
- Joseph Coolidge, Jr. to [Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough] re: clock 1827 March 31, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:710)
- John H[artwell] Cocke to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1827 April 3, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:711)
- Joseph Coolidge, Jr. to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough re: clock 1827 April 3, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:712)
- Turner Bynum, guardian for William Carr, to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1827 April 6, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:713)
- E[dward] Lowber to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1827 April 12, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 7:714)
- Bernard Peyton to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1827 April 21, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 7:715)